Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
- Box: 54, Folder: 12 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Basic Approaches to Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By John S. Bugas. Address before the Sixth Annual Forum of Agriculture, Labor and Industry, University of Wyoming, Laramie, WY, July 31, 1950. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Ford Dental Plan, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By Ford Motor Co. For Salaried Employes and Their Families. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Ford's Detroit Inner-City Recruiting Program, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Horsepower and Horse Sense, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By Henry Ford II. Address before the American Newspaper Publishers Association, New York, NY, April 28, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Industrial Relations - 1975, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By John S. Bugas. Address before the Labor and Industrial Relations Center, Michigan State University, East Lansing, MI, April 24, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: John S. Bugas to Robert Keys, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By Ford News Bureau; John S. Bugas. Correspondence. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Labor Law and Group Ethics, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By William T. Gossett. Address before the Church-Industry Group of the Detroit Employers' Association, Kirk-in-the-Hills, Bloomfield Hills, MI, April 20, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Looking Ahead in Labor Relations, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By John S. Bugas. Address before the Chicago Chamber of Commerce, Chicago, IL, April 26, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: management Views Financing of Hospital and Medical Care, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By Malcolm L. Denise. Address before the Second Institute for Hospital Administrators, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, MI, April 2, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Management's Role in Politics, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By J. Philip Martin. Address before the Society for the Advancement of Management Spring Management Conference, Detroit, MI, May 21, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Note to Editors, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By Lincoln-Mercury News Bureau. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Obligations of Business Management, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By Henry Ford II. Address before th Chamber of Commerce of the United States, Washington, DC, April 29, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Partners in Freedom, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By William T. Gossett. Address before the Association of Governing Boards of State Universities and Allied Institutions, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, MI, October 2, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Political Action: A New Dimension of Responsibility for Management, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By Thomas R. Reid. Address before the American Management Association General Management Conference, Los Angeles, CA, January 20, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Release AM Papers Thursday April 17 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By Ford News Bureau. press release. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Release Ams Friday April 11 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By Ford News Bureau. Press release. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Release Ams Friday, April 11, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 22: Release April 17, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 23: Release April 18, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 24: Release April 23, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 25: Release April 28, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 26: Release April 30, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 27: Release April 7, 1947., Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 28: Release August 11, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 29: Release August 13, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 30: Release August 2, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 31: Release August 2, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 32: Release August 28, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 33: Release August 3, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 34: Release August 4, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 35: Release August 5, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 36: Release August 5, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 37: Release February 27, 1948, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 38: Release February 5, 1948, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 39: Release February 5, 1948, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 40: Release July 17, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 41: Release July 18, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 42: Release July 22, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 43: Release June 11, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 44: Release June 11, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By Ford News Bureau; Ernest R. Breech. press release. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Release June 15, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 46: Release June 15, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 47: Release June 27, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 48: Release June 9, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 49: Release March 26, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 50: Release March 31, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 51: Release May 11, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 52: Release May 11, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 53: Release May 12, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 54: Release May 15, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 55: Release May 20, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 56: Release May 23, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 57: Release May 7, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 58: Release May 8, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 59: Release May 8, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 60: Release September 22, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 61: Release September 8, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 62: Release Sunday April 13 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By Lincoln-Mercury News Bureau. press release. Item is in English.
  - Item 63: Release Sunday April 20, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 64: Release Sunday March 30 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 65: Release Sunday, April 6, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 66: Release Thursday, April 10, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 67: Release Thursday, September 4, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 68: Spring model Lincolns, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By Ford Motor Co. Photograph + caption. Item is in English.
  - Item 69: Statement by Theodore O. Yntema, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By Theodore Yntema. Address before the Subcommittee on Antitrust and Monopoly of the Committee on the Judiciary, United State Senate, February 4-5, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 70: Sunday, April 13, 1947, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By Lincoln-Mercury News Bureau. Monday, Oct. 6, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 71: The Best Interests of American Workers, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By John S. Bugas. Address before the Mountain States Employers Council, Denver, CO, January 24, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 72: The Challenge to Engineers, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By Ernest R. Breech. Address before the Detroit Section, Society of Automotive Engineers, Dearborn, MI, Wednesday Dec. 31, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 73: The Evolution of Mass Production, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Item 74: Union Monopoly vs. The Public Interest, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By Ernest R. Breech. Address before the Nashville, Tennessee, Chamber of Commerce, Vanderbilt University, January 23, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 75: Unionization of Foremen at Ford Motor Company, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By William T. Gossett. Address before the Senate Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, Washington, DC, February 16, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 76: Voluntary Political Contribution Plan a Part of The Ford Effective Citizenship Program, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By Civic and Governmental Affairs Office. June 1, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 77: Wage Inflation: Public Enemy No. 1, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By Theodore O. Yntema. Address before the American Life Underwriters Association, Chicago, IL, October 11, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 78: Wanted: An Economic Breakthrough, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
    By Henry Ford II. Address before Students and Guests of Yale University, New Haven, CT, February 19, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 79: What the New Ford Contract means to us and to you, Publication (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Box: 54, Folder: 13 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Equal Employment Opportunity Affirmative Action Program, Publication (Box 54, Folder 13)
    By Fischer & Porter Company. September 1979. Item is in English.
- Box: 54, Folder: 14 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Your Job and ours, Publication (Box 54, Folder 14)
    By Florence Stove Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 55, Folder: 1 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: "The New Soviet Machine Age--A Look at the Automation in Russia", Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    By Nevin Bean. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Bargaining and Economic Growth, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    By Henry Ford II. Address before the 18th Annual Meeting of the American Society of Corporate Secretaries, Coronado, CA, June 22, 1964. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Employee Recreation at the Ford Motor Company, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    By Ford Motor Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Let's Keep Education Competitive: An Address by Henry Ford at Yale University, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    By Henry Ford II. Address before the Yale Alumni Fund Association Annual Dinner, New York, NY, December 2, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: One Solution to Our Problems: An Address by Henry Ford II at a Commonewealth Club Luncheon, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    By Henry Ford II. Address before the Commonwealth Club Luncheon, San Francisco, CA, February 8, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Production for Peace and Freedom: An Address by Henry Ford, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    By Henry Ford II. Address before the Automotive and Aviation Parts Manufacturers, Cleveland, OH, September 29, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Regulations Governing the Safe Operationof Electric Cranes, Locomotive Cranes, Elevatros, Railroad Equipment, and Hoist Engines, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Release January 15, 1947., Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Report of Management Meeting, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    By Ford Motor Company. March 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Report of Management Meeting, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    By Ford Motor Company. May 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Report of Management Meeting (Number 12, October 1948), Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    By Ford Motor Company. no.12 (1948:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Safety Regulations for Drivers of Vehicles, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Speech before the National Forum on Trucking Industial Relations, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    By Mel B. Lindquist. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Ford Foreman Program, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    By Archie A. Pearson. Address before the American Management Association Production Conference, Chicago, IL, November 19, 1948. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Union Monopoly vs. The Public Interest, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
    By Ernest R. Breech. Address before the Nashville, Tennessee, Chamber of Commerce, Vanderbilt University, January 23, 1958. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 55, Folder: 2 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: "Setting Your Course" Salaried Employee's Handbook, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: "The Years Ahead" General Retirement Plan for Salaried and certain other Employees, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Ford Motor Company. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A Guide to Research, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Ford Motor Company Training Department. Course no.3754: Writing Techinques: Staff Development. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: America's Secret Weapon, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Ernest R. Breech. Address before the Economic Club of Detroit, September 11,1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: America's Secret Weapon, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Ernest R. Breech. Address before the Economic Club of Detroit, September 11,1950. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Automation: A News Department Release, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Automotive Body, Chassis, and Engine Design Training Programs, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Bargaining and Economic Growth, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Henry Ford II. Address before the 18th Annual Meeting of the American Society of Corporate Secretaries, Coronado, CA, June 22, 1964. Copy 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Double Overtime Pay, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Theodore O. Yntema. Address before the Joint Committee of General Subcommittee on Labor and Select Subcommittee on Labor of the Committee on Education and Labor, Washington, DC, February 28, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Double Overtime Pay, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By John S. Bugas. Address before the Subcommittee on Labor, Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, United State Senate, Washington, DC, July 8, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Factory Facts from Ford, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Ford Motor Company: Pamphlet for College Graduates, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Ford Motor Company's Work with Profit Sharing, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By D. Kenneth Laub. An Investigation by the Detroit Evening News, November 24, 1914. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Helpful Hints and Advice to Ford Employes, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: How to Become a Foreman through the Management Development Program, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Industrial Relations-1975, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By John S. Bugas. Address before the Labor and Industrial Relations Center, Michigan State University, East Lansing, MI, April 24, 1957. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Industrial Relations-1975: An Address by John S. Bugas, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By John S. Bugas. Address before the Labor and Industrial Relations Center, Michigan State University, East Lansing, MI, April 24, 1957. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Industrial Relations--Unfinished Business, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By John S. Bugas. Address before the Institute of Industrial Relations, College of the Holy Cross, Worchester, MA, April 27, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Industrial Training: Basic Training Courses, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Ford Highland Park Apprentice School. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Les Aspects Recents de la Politique Du Travail De Ford, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Samuel M. Levin. Extrait de la Revue Economique Internationale. Item is in French.
  - Item 21: News Letter, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Ford Motor Company. Special Edition, January 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: News Letter, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Ford Motor Company. January 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: News Letter, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Ford Motor Company. March 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Obligations of Business Management, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Henry Ford II. Address before the Chamber of Commerce of the United States, April 29, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Official 100 Facts Taught by the Teachers of the Ford English School, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 26: Preparing High School Graduates and Others for Skilled Work in Industry, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Frederick E. Searle. Address before the American Management Association Personnel Conference, Chicago, IL, February 16, 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Production Management Training Program, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Ford Motor Company Training Department. Cover page only. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Release in PMs of Tuesday, August 1, 1950, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Ford Motor Company. press release. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Safety Training, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Ford Motor Company Training Department. File Number 760-83. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: The Challenge of Human Engineering, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Henry Ford II. Address before the Society of Automotive Engineers Annual Meeting, Detroit, MI, January 9, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: The Challenge of Human Engineering, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Henry Ford II. Address before the Society of Automotive Engineers Annual Meeting, Detroit, MI, January 9, 1946. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: The Challenge of Human Engineering, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Henry Ford II. Address before the Society of Automotive Engineers Annual Meeting, Detroit, MI, January 9, 1946. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: The Ford Idea in Education, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 34: The Human Bridge, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 35: Training Airplane Workers in Willow Run and Elsewhere, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Frederick E. Searle. Address before the American Vocational Associatioon. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Union Monopoly vs. The Public Interest, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Ernest R. Breech. Address before the Nashville, Tennessee, Chamber of Commerce, Vanderbilt University, January 23, 1958. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Use of Handicapped Workers, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Frederick E. Searle. Address before the Silver Bay Industrial Conference, Silver Bay, NY, July 29, 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Wage Inflation: Public Enemy No. 1, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Theodore O. Yntema. Address before the American Life Underwriters Association, Chicago, IL, October 11, 1957. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Where Are the Salesmen Coming From?, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Walker A. Williams. Address before the American Management Association, New York, NY, March 16, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Which Road to Security?, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    By Ernest R. Breech. Address before the Industrial Information Institute, Youngstown, OH, September 27, 1949. Item is in English.
- Box: 55, Folder: 3 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A Moral Basis for our Leadership, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
    By Benson Ford. Address before the Detroit Round Table of the National Conference of Christians and Jews, Detroit, MI, November 13, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Political Challenge to Business and Industry, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
    By Henry Ford II. Address before the Economic Club of New York, New York, NY, April 28, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Aircraft School; Curriculum Bulletin, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Apprenticeship Standards, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Ford Recreation Bulletin; Introduction, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
    By Ford Motor Company. no.1 (1946:Dec. 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Fortune: The Birth of Ford, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
    By Ford Motor Company. v.35:no.5 91947:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Henry Ford Trade School, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: News Letter, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
    By Ford Motor Company. October 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: News Letter, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
    By Ford Motor Company. February 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: One Solution to our Problems, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
    By Henry Ford II. Address before the Commonwealth Club Luncheon, San Francisco, CA, February 8, 1946. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Our Job is Your Job; The Story of Ford Public Relations, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
    By Charles Carll. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Report of Management Meeting, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Return of the Salesman, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
    By J. R. Davis. Address before the Sales Executives Club of New York, New York, NY, March 15, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Revolution on the Rouge, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
    By Andre Fontaine. Reprinted from Collier's, November 15, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Suggestion Plan; For the Employees of the Ford Motor Company, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Supervisor's Manual: Hourly Personnel, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: The Rewards of Curiosity, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
    By Benson Ford. Address before the St. Louis and St. Louis County Chambers of Commerce, St. Louis, MO, September 22, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Why No Postwar $1,000 Car?, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
    By Ernest R. Breech. Item is in English.
- Box: 55, Folder: 4 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A Political Challenge to Business and Industry, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    By Henry Ford II. Address before the Economic Club of New York, New York, NY, April 28, 1949. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A report on the Ford Employees United Foundation Contribution Plan, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    By Employee Services Department Industrial Relations Staff Ford Motor Co. March, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: An Analysis of The Ford Type Plan for Supplemental Unemployment Compensation, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    By NAM (National Association of Manufacturers). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Big Labor in the Democratic Society, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    By William T. Gossett. Address before the Chicago Bar Association Annual Meeting, Chicago, IL, June 15, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Five Jobs For Young Men, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    By Benson Ford. Address before the Los Angeles Chamber of Commerce, Los Angeles, CA, February 28, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Organizational Chart, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Salaried Employee History, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    By Ford Motor Company. Blank personnel form. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Salaried Personnel Application For Employment, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Some Unfinished Business For Young Americans, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    By Benson Ford. Address before the Department of Business Administration, Michigan State College, East Lansing, MI, December 8, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Supervisor's Manual: Salaried Personnel, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: The Challenge of Human Engineering, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    By Henry Ford II. Address before the Society of Automotive Engineers Annual Meeting, Detroit, MI, January 9, 1946. Copy 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Ford Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    By Ford Motor Company. June, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Ford Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    By Ford Motor Company. June 1955 Copy 2. Item is in English.